fxstreet.com 2003-12-04

# FXstreet DISCLAIMER & Privacy Policy

**1\. DISCLAIMER**

This web-site is an information site only. Accordingly we make no warranties or guarantees in respect of the content.   
These publications do not take into account the investment objectives, financial situation or particular needs of any particular person. Investors should obtain individual financial advice based on their own particular circumstances before making an investment decision on the basis of the recommendations in this web-site. 

Whilst we try to ensure that all of the information provided on this web-site is kept up-to-date and accurate we accept no responsibility for any use made of the information provided. 

We provide links from this web-site to other sites owned by or operated by third parties. We are not responsible or liable for any of the content posted on such third party web-sites and are not and will not be responsible or liable, whether directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused, or alleged to be caused, by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, or goods or services available on such external sites or resources. 

These terms and conditions shall be governed by Spanish law and any dispute shall be referred exclusively to the Spanish courts. 

**2\. PRIVACY POLICY**

At FOREXSTREET SL maintaining trust and confidence is a high priority. We understand that privacy is an important issue for our valued registered users, as well as visitors to our website fxstreet.com. Whether you are a registered user of fxstreet.com, or a visitor browsing our website, we want you to understand how we work to protect your privacy in the event we collect and use information about you, and the steps we take to safeguard that information. 

GENERAL INFORMATION ABOUT BROWSING FOREXSTREET SL WEBSITE 

At FOREXSTREET SL, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We will not sell or share your personal information with third parties, regardless of whether you are a registered user or just a visitor to our site. 

At FOREXSTREET SL , no personal information is retrieved from FOREXSTREET SL server when a registered user or visitor browses the public (pre-login) areas of our websites. Although FOREXSTREET SL uses website data to improve the content and services offered to its website visitors, such data is reported on an aggregate, anonymous basis, and we associate no personal information with such gathering of data. Such data may include: how many people visit our websites; the pages they visit; how long they stay on our websites; and the domain name of the site visitors connect from (e.g., yahoo.com). 

A WORD ABOUT COOKIES 

Cookies are small text files that a website transfers to your hard drive or browser to help you move faster through that particular website, or for tracking your website usage. FOREXSTREET SL does not use cookies to gather personal information such as a person's name or email address. We do, however, use cookies to facilitate login process to our registered users.   
Please be assured that any information we gather by the use of a cookie is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis. 

Third parties might also create cookies when you access their sites through links posted on our sites. We do not have access to these cookies or any information that these cookies may contain. Please contact the third party site for more information on their policies regarding cookies. Although we expect third parties to adhere to our privacy policies and terms and conditions of use, we are not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. 

A WORD ABOUT HYPERLINKS 

FOREXSTREET SL's website may contain hyperlinks or "links" to other sites, and other sites may "link" to our sites. Websites linking to and from our sites may have privacy practices different from FOREXSTREET SL's. This Website Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by our websites. FOREXSTREET SL is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of sites you link to, and we have no control over the use or protection of information provided by you or collected by those sites. If you elect to link to a co-branded website or to a linked website, you may be asked to provide registration or other information. Please note that the information you are providing is going to a third party, and you should familiarize yourself with the privacy policy provided by that third party. 

NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION 

In the event visitors provide FOREXSTREET SL with nonpublic personal information about themselves (e.g., name, address, phone number, email address) for the purpose of receiving information about our products and advertisers services, or if you are a FOREXSTREET SL registered user and we obtain from you personal information about you in the course of providing you with our services, the following are the steps we take to safeguard such nonpublic personal information ("Personal Information"). 

SECURITY PROCEDURES: 

FOREXSTREET SL restricts access to Personal Information about you to: 

Those of our employees who need to know that information in order to provide the services you receive from us.   
Those recommended brokers that we have introduced to you, and who need to know that information in order to assist you in your foreing exchange needs. 

To protect the security of Personal Information, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with Spain's standards for guarding the information we collect about you 

. 

INFORMATION WE COLLECT: 

In providing you with financial products and services, or information about such services, Man Financial may collect the following types of Personal Information: 

Information we receive from you when you request to be contacted by one of our recommended brokers, whether written or electronic, or on other forms (including on-line forms). This information would include your name, last name, city, country, e-mail address, and telephone number.   
Information we receive from you when you register to our service "My FX" thruough on-line form. This information would include your name, last name, country, e-mail address, and language. 

WEBSITE PRIVACY STATEMENT UPDATES 

FOREXSTREET SL may, from time to time, make changes to this Website Privacy Statement. We recommend that frequent visitors to our websites reread this Website Privacy Statement periodically to learn of any updates and changes we have made to this Statement. Should you become a FOREXSTREET SL registered user by obtaining a user ID and password and completing our on-line form, we will notify you of any changes we make to this Statement in the following manner. The first time you log on one of our websites after we have modified our Website Privacy Statement, we will require you to click-through our revised Statement. 

If you wish to correct any inaccurate or outdated personal information, or if you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, email us at forex@fxstreet.com
